myhomedesign.in 2015-05-01

# Home Design & Build Community, Home Interior Design Ideas Privacy Policy @ My Home Design

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information **My Home Design  **website belonging to MHMD Ecomm Pvt. Ltd., hereinafter referred to as MHMD, collects and how we use and disclose that information. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the MHMD Terms of Use. By your use of and/or registration on MHMD, you expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use MHMD. MHMD reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice. The date of the most recent revision will appear on this page, and your continued use of MHMD will constitute your acceptance of any revisions of this Privacy Policy. 

If you choose to use MHMD, we may require you to provide personal information as indicated on the MHMD site, whether as part of the registration process or in connection with your use of the MHMD site. 

We collect and store the following information:

  * Email address, IP address, and physical contact information;
  * Design Guides, comments, reviews, images, other uploaded content, questions and answers, discussion area posts and other messages, including correspondence between MHMD and you; and
  * Other information automatically collected whenever you interact with MHMD, such as computer sign-on data, statistics on page views and traffic to and from the MHMD site. For example, we use "cookies" (small data files that are placed on your computer) so that we can recognize your browser and record such interaction information. You can disable the use of cookies through your browser settings; however this is likely to affect your ability to use certain features of the MHMD site.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not use the MHMD site or services or use it under parental guidance. This is required so that you do not knowingly or unknowingly engage the services of any professional without being authorized to do so. 

We may use your information as follows:

  * to provide MHMD services;
  * to verify your identity when you sign in;
  * to encourage safe online experiences and enforce our policies;
  * to customize users' experience, analyze site usage, improve and measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;
  * to identify your reviews as your own;
  * to communicate administrative announcements when we need to provide users with information that may affect their use of MHMD;
  * to communicate marketing and promotional offers to our users;
  * to provide customer service; and
  * to deliver to you information that is targeted to your interests. Upon receipt of the first communication of this type, you will have the opportunity to opt-out of future communications by following unsubscribe instructions described within the communication. As part of your registration on MHMD, you agree that you may receive certain administrative communications from MHMD, and you will not be able to opt out of receiving such administrative communications.

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your consent. However, we may share certain information as follows:

  * to affiliates of MHMD that we control and that are subject to this Privacy Policy or follow privacy practices at least as protective as ours;
  * to third parties to enforce our Terms of Use and other MHMD agreements and policies, or to protect anyone's rights, property, or safety;
  * to third parties to respond to claims that photos or other content that you may upload violate other's rights;
  * to an acquirer of all or substantially all of the equity, assets or business/es of MHMD;
  * to service providers who help with our business operations and assist in the delivery of MHMD services under obligations of confidentiality;
  * to law enforcement or other government officials in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities;
  * as otherwise required by law.

To prevent unauthorized access, promote data security, and encourage appropriate use of information, we use a variety of tools to assist in the protection of your personal information. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, so we make no guarantees. 

You agree that we may transfer your personal information to other countries as required in connection with any of the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

We may provide links to websites operated by companies other than MHMD that we believe may be of interest to you. Except as set forth above, we do not disclose your personal information to the operators of such third-party websites without obtaining your consent. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third-party sites. If you choose to visit one of these third-party sites, you should review the privacy policy and Terms & Conditions posted on such third-party site/s to understand how that party collects, uses and discloses your personal information. 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [contact.mhmd@gmail.com](mailto:contact.mhmd@gmail.com)
